http://gcmindia.org/terms-conditions/

Skip to content (Press Enter)
Self Employment & Empowerment
GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES is committed to the ethical collection, retention and use of information that you provide to us about yourself (“Personal Information”) on this site www.gcmindia.org
Your Personal Information may comprise the following:
a. your name
b. a user ID and password of your choice
c. your email and mailing address
d. your telephone number
e. your payment processing details
f. any other data as GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES may require
The following Privacy Policy sets forth our understanding with you on the collection, use and protection of your Personal Information. Please read the entire Privacy Policy.
YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR CONSENT TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CONTAINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY (AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME) AND YOU SHALL BE BOUND BY THE SAME.
Collection of Information
Site Browsing: You browse the Site anonymously. We do not require you to identify yourself or reveal any Personal Information while browsing through the Site. However, you may not be able to access certain sections of the Site or interact with us without supplying us with Personal Information. For instance, you would not be able to transact at the Site or make any donations at the Site, without providing the Site with Personal Information. If you desire to register yourself at the Site, you would be required to provide your Personal Information.
While you are browsing through the Site, the Site’s operating system may automatically record some general information (“General Information”) about your visit such as:
• the date and time you visit the Site, along with the address of the previous website you were visiting, if you linked to us from another website
• the type of browser you are using (such as Internet Explorer version ‘X’)
• which ‘hit’ it is on the Site
The General Information is not Personal Information. GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES’s tracking system does not record personal information about individuals or link this information to any Personal Information collected from you.
The General Information is used by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES for statistical analysis, for tracking overall traffic patterns on the Site and to gauge the public interest in GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES and the Site. Such General Information may be shared by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES with any person, at GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES’s discretion.
Cookies: “Cookies” are small amounts of data that a website can send to a web browser on a visitor’s computer. The cookie is stored on a visitor’s computer. A cookie may enable the site holder to track how a visitor navigates through its site and the areas in which they show interest. This is like a traffic report: it tracks trends and behaviours but does not identify individuals. Information gathered may include date and time of visits, pages viewed, time spent at the site, and the site visited just before and just after the GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES site.
Types of Cookies
Cookies can be set to expire: on a specified date after a specific period when a transaction has been completed or when a user turns off his/her browser.
A cookie that is erased from memory when a visitor’s browser closes is called a “session” cookie. Cookies that expire based on a time set by the Web server are called “persistent” cookies.
Persistent cookies may be used in some cases, for example, to recognize when a visitor returns to a website. The web browser will send the cookie information from the initial visit back to the website. This is useful to the visitor if he or she has established a password at a website and wants to be identified by that site to perform a function or transaction.
To browse anonymously, you may set your browser to disable cookies or delete cookies. Please note that disabling cookies for some services will impact ability to use that service.
Refusing Cookies on GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES’s Website
Customers may choose not to accept cookies. Your web browser may alert and permit you to refuse cookies. When you receive an alert, you may choose at that time to refuse that cookie. If the use of cookies is a concern to you, then please make sure your browser has this capability, and that you set your browser to alert you accordingly.
Newer browser versions allow you to be alerted or to automatically refuse cookies. You may need to download a more current version of your web browser from your service provider in order to obtain this option.
Note: Some product features and services provided by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES require you to accept a cookie in order to be able to use the functionality or service. These cookies are used to establish a link between the user and the application server. The cookies contain unique session IDs, and no customer data is stored on the cookies.
Usage of Information
Personal information will be used by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES for internal purposes including the following:
sending you inter alia emails, features, promotional material, surveys, brochures, catalogues, GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES Annual Report, newsletters, reminders for donations, regular updates on the utilisation of donations by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES and other updates.processing your donations to GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES and purchases of GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES products on the Site.delivering the GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES products you have purchased on the Site /Receipt for donations made by you to GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES.maintaining an internal confidential database of all the Personal Information collected from visitors to the Site.evaluating and administering the Site and GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES’s activities, responding to any problems that may arise and gauging visitor trends on the Site.
Disclosure of Personal Information by Great Commission Ministries
Within GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES, access to Personal Information collected by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES will be given only to those persons who are authorised by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES and third parties hired by GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES to perform administrative services. GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES will provide access to third parties for inter alia entering and managing Personal Information in GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES’s Database, processing your orders or donations preparing address labels, sending emails, which require such third parties to have access to your Personal Information. GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES cannot guarantee that such parties will keep your Personal Information confidential and GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES will not be liable in any manner for any loss of confidentiality attributable to such third parties.
GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES may share Personal Information with any of persons who are associated with GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES, including companies and non-governmental organisations affiliated with GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES in any manner. GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES will retain ownership rights over such information and will share only such portions of the Personal Information as it deems fit.
GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES is not liable in any manner whatsoever for the loss, damage (whether direct, indirect, consequential or incidental) or harm caused to you by the misuse of your Personal Information by a third party who is not an employee of GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES.
Notwithstanding anything contained herein or any other contract between you and GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES, GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES reserves the right to disclose any Personal Information about you without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any requirement of law, regulation, legal request or legal investigation, to conduct investigations of breaches of law, to protect the Site, to protect GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES and its property, to fulfil your requests, to protect our visitors and other persons and if required by the policy of GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES.
Security
GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES endeavours to use up-to-date security measures to protect your Personal Information. The Site is a LETS ENCRYPT approved site.
GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES however does not make any express or implied warranty with respect to the security measures that it may employ from time to time for the protection of the Personal Information.
Links to other Websites
The Site contains links to other websites for the benefit of its visitors. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such other websites. GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES is not expressly or impliedly responsible for, or liable to any loss or damage caused to you by the collection, use and retention of Personal Information by such website in any manner whatsoever. It is important that you review the privacy policies of all websites you visit before you disclose any information to such websites.
Variation of the Privacy Policy
GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES shall be absolutely entitled at its sole discretion from time to time add to, alter, delete or modify any of the terms and conditions contained herein. Such changes, additions, alterations, deletions or modifications shall be binding on you once you visit the Site after the Privacy Policy has been so amended.
Copyright Protection
All content on this Site including graphics, text, icons, interfaces, audio clips, logos, images and software is the property of GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES and/or its content suppliers and is protected by Indian and international copyright laws. The arrangement and compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all content on this Site is the exclusive property of GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES and protected by Indian and international copyright laws. Permission is given to use the resources of this Site only for the purposes of making enquiries, donating or placing an order for the purchase of GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES products. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance, of the content on this Site can only be made with the express permission of GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES. All other trademarks, brands and copyrights other than those belonging to GREAT COMMISSION MINISTRIES belong to their respective owners and are their property.
